- What's her name?
- I don't know.
(Sheldon:)And you're going to let her
handle my food?
(Penny:)Nancy. Her name is Nancy.
(Sheldon:)I think you're just making that up.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I'm sorry about your hamburger,
okay? I just don't wanna be a waitress.
(Leonard:)Cheeseburger. I get a cheeseburger.
- Fine. Cheeseburger.
- Maybe I'd be better off with Nancy.
(Penny:)So, what do you think?
I mean, this could be a business, right?
- How many of these can you make a day?
- Mm. About 20.
(Sheldon:)And how much profit do you make
per Penny Blossom?
- I don't know. Like, 50 cents. I'm not sure.
- No, of course you're not. All right.
(Sheldon:)Ten dollars a day times five days a week
times 52 weeks a year is $2600.
- That's all?
- Before taxes.
(Penny:)Well, I don't have to pay taxes
on this stuff.
(Sheldon:)The Internal Revenue Service
would strongly disagree.
(Sheldon:)But if you took advantage
of modern marketing techniques...
...and optimized
your manufacturing process...